Contact

8475297792 (Mobile) emilyclarke30@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/emily-clarkern-bsn-cmsrn-81021a12 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

CCMS

Microsoft Excel

QNXT

Certifications

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse

Registered Nurse

Standard Teaching License Type 03&09

Basic Life Saving Certification

Emily Clarke, RN, BSN, CMSRN

Registered Nurse at Loyola Home Care and Adult Geriatric Primary Care Nurse Practitioner student at Lewis University

Oak Park, Illinois

Summary

Hi- I am a dedicated third-year Adult Gerontology Primary Care
Nurse Practitioner student looking to work with a passionate Primary
Care preceptor starting Fall 2020. I am registered nurse with ten
years of clinical experience in healthcare. I am a flexible, quick
learner who adapts quickly to change while enjoying challenges.
I am self-motivated, compassionate, and reliable with a desire to
learn, experience, and provide primary care medicine as a student
nurse practitioner.

Experience

Loyola Home Care RN, Case Manager May 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Oak Brook, IL

Vanguard Homecare Nurse Case Manager July 2012 - May 2018 (5 years 11 months) Greater Chicago Area

Maintain a strong reputation for high levels of patient satisfaction, excellent interpersonal skills with colleagues and patients, highly self motivated and organized.

- Developed and implemented individualized patient care plans and goals based on collaboration with patient, physicians and multi-disciplinary team members.
- Exceptional critical assessment skills with acknowledgment from peers and patients.
- Acknowledged for superior communication skills with patient families and colleagues.

Experienced clinical assessment skills and patient teaching: IV infusion/
Antibiotic/TPN, Port-A-Cath/PICC Line/Groshong Care/Peripheral Line,
Urinary Catheter Care/Urostomy Care/Nephrosotmy Care, Complex Wound
Care including wound vacs, Ostomy Care, G-Tube Care, Tracheotomy Care,
Oxygen Care/Teaching, Diabetic Teaching, Cardiac Teaching, Medication
Management.

West Suburban Medical Center
Registered Staff Nurse, ICU
January 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 7 months)
Oak Park, IL

Developed and implemented critical care assessment and communication skills while serving junior leadership roles.

- Experienced critical care assessment: ECG monitoring, 12-Lead ECG, hemodynamic monitoring and medication titrations, ventilator care, trach care, insulin drips, pacemaker assessments, post-op assessments, hypothermia training, stroke/neuro assessments, blood transfusions, radiology interpretation, wound care/colostomy care. Catheter, NG/OG tubes and IV training and experienced.
- · Safety leader/educator for the ICU.
- Developed, educated and implemented infection control evidence based practice research project.
- Educated patient/families on healthcare status and conditions.

Gottlieb Memorial Hospital
Wound Care/Patient Care Tech
December 2009 - December 2010 (1 year 1 month)
Gottlieb Memorial Hospital

Contributed to the development of the scope of practice for a wound care tech through communication, collaboration and continued education.

- Assisted during wound care treatment: debridement, wound vacs, post-op/trauma/burn wounds.
- Collaborated and communicated with nurses and doctors: improvement of patient care, promoted a comfortable and safe working environment, participated in all educational experiences.

Chicago Public Schools
Educator
August 2001 - August 2006 (5 years 1 month)
Chicago, IL

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Chicago Public Schools, IL

Sampson County Public Schools, NC

Park Forest/Chicago Heights School District, IL 2001 - 2006

Educator

Critically assessed, adapted and applied classroom management skills; established positive and productive rapport with both students and colleagues.

- Assessed and modified curriculum to meet the needs of physically and mentally challenged students.
- Developed and maintained successful management skills.

Education

Lewis University

MSN, Adult Geriatric Nurse Practitioner (2017 - 2021)

Resurrection University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2010)

Northern Illinois University

Bachelor's Degree, Education · (1996 - 2001)